♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Hey, great idea bringing
the couch out here
from your den, Peter.
Yeah, Lois and I
dragged it out here last night
for a little hump sesh,
so I figured I'd let it dry.
"Couch." That's
one of those words
that if you say it over and over
it starts to sound silly.
Joe, you need to take
a class on small talk.
You're not gonna believe
this-- I'm in one.
It sure is cloudy today.
Good. You could have
also responded to Janet,
who said her son died.
I'm sorry your son died
on such a cloudy day.
All right, kids,
here's your bacon.
I call the paper towel!
Aw, damn it!
Ha-ha! You got to move fast
when Meg's at the table, Brian.
All right, well, I get the box
when we have pizza for dinner.
Uh-uh. It
doesn't work that way.
You got to call it
when it's happening.
Good morning, family.
I'll be out front
with the guys
if anybody needs me.
Peter, I thought
we were gonna try
to get the garden going
again today.
I know, sweetie, but then
I realized how stupid that is.
Okay, bye. You guys
are my everything.
Why'd you ever marry him?
Believe it or not, he used to
look like a young Gene Hackman.
That's... that-that's
not even good.
It's gone!
What? What's gone?
Our drinking couch!
Somebody must've stole it!
You left a couch
out on the curb?
Well, somebody probably thought
it was trash and took it.
You said you were gonna bring
the couch right back in!
What were you thinking?
I'll tell you what I was thinking.
I was thinking we lived
in a safe neighborhood.
But apparently,
I was wrong!
Wait, you're saying
you were wr-wr...
wr-wro...
wr-wrrr...
Oh, I get it--
the Fonz can't say "wrong."
No, Peter, he's 70--
he's having a stroke.
Wow, Peter, I think
starting a community watch
is a great idea.
Yeah, I even got shirts
made up for us.
This is quality work.
Where did you get these?
Via the Web?
Hey, listen, Joe, um,
you think you
can get us all guns?
No, Peter,
they're too dangerous.
Besides, you can't
just go get a gun,
you have to be certified
in gun safety,
go through an extensive
background screening process.
Got 'em.
Whoa. How'd you
get 'em so quick?
Eh, it was easy-- like
pressing that "easy" button
at the office
supply store.
Hey, thanks for all your help.
No problem.
Why don't you go ahead
and hit the "easy" button.
Okay.
What did I just do?
Don't worry about it.
Hey, Quagmire,
you're a sex guy.
You watch any good,
uh... pornos lately?
I mean...
I-I guess.
So what's your pleasure?
What kind of
movies you like?
I don't know.
MILF stuff's kind of cool.
What-what about you?
Me? I have very
particular tastes.
I like a soapy bottom.
What?
Soft-core
soaped-up butts,
like from a PG-13
camp movie.
I can't get enough of it.
Drives me wild.
Okay, let's talk
about something else.
All right. Uh...
it's kind of too cool
for the air-conditioner
and too warm for
the heater, huh?
Ah, got to walk
that boner off, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, guys, you
better come with me.
There's some weird, big-nose
guy hiding in the bushes
outside some
chick's house.
"My heart always
timidly hides itself
behind my mind."
"I set out
to bring down stars
from the sky..."
"Ow. Ow.
"Oh, my God,
four men are beating me.
"My arm.
I think it is broken.
"Who are you guys?
"Why? Why?
"I'll give you anything if
you would only stop hitting me.
"Please stop pulling my nose.
"It is not fake.
"I think I am dying.
Please take me to the hospital."
Your words have bewitched me.
I need your arms around me.
Come to
my chamber at once.
"Come to my chamber
at once."
And bring pound cake.
"And bring pound cake."
Peter, please
come to bed.
Enough of the
community watch.
We live on a very
safe street.
Lois, you wouldn't believe
the things we see out there.
There was a kid riding his bike
while holding a tennis racket.
For real.
Come on! Let's fool around,
or watch a movie,
or finally click that
"Crackle" icon on the TV.
Lois, I am
an unelected vigilante,
and I take my job
very seriously.
Like Serious George.
Hey, George, want
to go to the park?
Uh, thank you, but no.
It's a beautiful day--
lots of mischief to get into.
I don't doubt that,
but as you can see,
I'm pretty busy.
I'm trying to get
a head start on my taxes.
Oh, I see-- trying
to figure out a way
to deduct bananas?
Ah. 'Cause I eat
bananas. Terrific.
Hey, your inside,
so don't wear a hat.
Unless you're leaving,
which would be terrific also.
What the hell? Hey, you!
Step away from that table.
Brain fart. Window. Sorry.
Hold it right there!
I'm warning you!
Hands where I could see 'em.
♪ ♪
Cleveland Jr.?!
Mr. Griffin! You shot me!
Oh, my God!
Peter, where are you?
Peter? Okay, I'm starting
The Good Wife without you.
Phew! Heh.
Unlike you,
I just dodged a bullet.
Okay, next is the...
brown family.
Oh. Oh, my goodness.
I'm-I'm so sorry.
Sometimes I write
descriptions of my patients
to help me
remember them.
No, it's okay.
Our last name is Brown.
Oh, okay. Phew.
Ah, then this must be
"Chubster Dumb-Dumb."
I'm sorry, sir. No visitors.
Excuse me, I'll have you know
I'm the shooter!
So, uh, how's he doing?
"How's he doing"?!
How do you think he's doing!
You shot my son!
Look, Cleveland,
I-I'm real sorry.
I thought someone was breaking
into your house, and I panicked.
It was dark. I-I...
I don't know why
he didn't just say
it was him.
I couldn't hear you.
I was listening to music,
I went to turn it down,
and the next thing I know.
you shot me!
Why the hell were you
climbing in the window
of your own house
anyway?
My dad says opening the door
lets out too much
air-conditioning.
I already have a bullet
in my son,
I don't need one
in my wallet.
You wouldn't have fired
that gun if he was white!
That's not true--
I'll shoot anybody.
Joe, give me
your gun.
Here you go...
Hey, wait a second!
Look, let's all just calm down.
Calm down?!
I want this racist
out the room,
and I want him arrested!
Racist? I put these
gloves on for everybody.
Oh, oh, you're
talking to him.
Look, the police department has
deemed the shooting accidental.
Given the circumstances,
Peter was within his rights
to fire his weapon.
And what about my son's rights
not to be shot?!
Look, Cleveland...
Lat... Latisha?
I thought he had a gun.
I'd never want to do anything
to hurt you or your family.
You're my friend.
I was your friend.
Now, get out of here!
You're nothing but
a worthless bigot!
Wow, I really messed up.
I haven't felt this bad since
I drove by that speed sign.
Aw...
Hey, does anybody know
if Cleveland's coming by?
I was hoping to apologize
and collect his deposit
for the community watch shirts.
I talked to him earlier.
He, uh, he doesn't want
to be anywhere near you.
Hey, look-- they're talking
about the shooting.
Good evening.
Two nights ago
there was a shooting right here
in our own backyard.
The victim: a 14-year-old boy
named Cleveland Brown Jr.
Joining me tonight is
his father, Cleveland Brown.
So that's not really Quahog?
It's just a big picture?
Now, Mr. Brown, I understand
you're trying to get the police
to reopen the investigation.
That's right, Tom.
My family and I believe
this shooting was a hate crime,
and we'd like to see Mr. Griffin
held accountable
for his actions.
Hate crime? That's crazy!
I love all people!
I love blacks, I love Asians...
hell, I even love
gay Aborigines.
Wow, this is
just great, Peter.
Everyone in town
hates us now.
The cashier at the grocery store
told her to "push on,"
and then
she snapped her fingers,
and now I think she's my new
favorite lady in the world.
I don't understand.
I'm not a racist.
It's well documented
that my dream three-way
is S. Epatha Merkerson
and CCH Pounder.
S., this is CCH.
CCH, this is S.
It is my intention
that we conduct this
with both sexiness
and dignity.
Peter, this is a
hot-button issue.
I mean, you shot an
African-American kid.
Of course this isn't
just gonna go away.
Well, there's got to be something
I can do to make things right.
I'll just have to prove to everybody
that I'm not a racist.
How are you gonna do that?
Well, for starters,
I'm gonna head over
to the YMCA.
There's nothing
black guys like more
than out-of-shape
indoor-basketball white guys.
Hey! I'm trying
my best here.
And trying is
what matters most of all.
You're right, Peter.
We need to give
you a chance,
no matter what
color your skin is.
Come on, let's
play some ball.
"...and then Peter and his
new friends went for ice cream."
The end.
Okay, kids, are your parents
out of the room?
Good. Let's get back
to Sloppy Floppers magazine.
What are you doing?
Lois, to show I'm in touch
with what it's like
to be African-American,
I am gonna go to the middle
of the town square, get naked
and paint myself brown.
No, no, that's
offensive.
You can't pretend
to be black.
That's a stupid idea.
What?
It's a stupid idea!
You're a stupid man!
A stupid, stupid man!
Ow, you're hurting me!
Stop it, stop it, Lois!
No! I'm so sick
of your crap.
Why do you always
do these stupid things?
And why do you always announce
them to me before you do them?
Are you trying
to get a rise out of me?
Are you happy now?
Is this what you want?
Oh, no,
it's not what I want!
It's not what I want.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's never been this bad before.
What do we do?
What we always do.
I'm in charge of my head--
that much I know!
What the hell
are you doing on my property?
Look, it's time we
bury the hatchet.
So I brought a bottle
of your favorite booze.
Now let's just have a drink
and put this all behind us.
I don't want
nothing from you.
Well, hold on,
I got something else.
Cigars. We can smoke 'em
together, all happy,
like a bunch of douche bags
outside a wedding.
Peter, get out of here.
I'm never gonna forgive you
for what you did.
Aw, come on.
This'll change your mind.
Oh, my God!
Quick, do something!
It's not working.
Get rid of it!
Get your family
out of that house!
If they don't leave,
they'll die.
Round up your family
and get out
or you're all
gonna be sorry.
Get out, now!
See, kids, I told you
we'd make friends here.
I guess me getting transferred
by the Xerox Corporation
wasn't the worst thing
after all.
Oh, thank God, Joe.
Are you here to give me the
deposit for the shirts?
No, Peter, I'm here to place you
under arrest
for the attempted murder
of Cleveland Junior.
What are you talkin' about?
You know it was an accident.
Yeah, but let's just say,
public opinion has shifted.
And the boys upstairs said
they can no longer ignore it.
Who the hell are
the "boys upstairs?"
I have no idea.
There's no elevator.
But whoever they are,
they're pretty steamed
about this whole thing.
Peter, what-what's
going on?
They're taking me to jail!
Oh, my God!
Don't worry, Dad!
I'll send you a cake
with a file in it!
These are just the owner manuals
for all our kitchen appliances.
Well, guess I finally have time
to learn to reset the clock
on the coffee maker.
He never did.
You're-you're, uh...
you're not gonna
rape me, are you?
Of course I'm not
gonna rape you.
I'm gonna make you
fall in love with me.
Then... we'll
see what happens.
Oh, no.
It's already working.
Griffin, you have a visitor.
Carter? What are
you doing here?
Hello, Griffin.
I'd like to talk to you
about these charges
that have been
brought against you.
Why don't we go somewhere
a little more private?
I, uh, guess I'll see you
in a little bit?
It's gonna feel
like an eternity.
How is it that I'm only
just now meeting you?
Look, Carter, you
got to believe me.
I didn't shoot Cleveland
Junior because he was black!
Hey, you don't have
to tell me that.
But the media's out there
making you look like a monster,
all for exercising
your constitutional rights.
Grover's a monster.
But don't worry.
We're gonna get you out of this.
I'll be damned
if I'm gonna sit back
and let them do this
to one of my own.
What, you mean your family?
Huh?
Oh, yeah, yeah, that.
Yeah, right.
Look, I'm gonna
bail you out of here,
set you up with my lawyer,
and get these charges dropped.
Well, how you gonna do that?
Don't worry.
I'll come up with a good story,
and they'll eat it up.
Not like when I read
my JAG fan fiction
at the NCIS convention.
"JAG stood up and yelled,
"'Objection, Your Honor,
by Navy law.'
"He then turned
to the lady lawyer,
"the gal from the October Maxim,
"who still managed to be hot
"despite her sexless,
pageboy haircut.
Or perhaps because of it."
Boo!
Terrible!
Right branch of the military,
wrong investigative arm!
And I was trying to
get back into my house,
and my neighbor,
Mr. Griffin, shot me.
He said
he felt threatened by me,
and that hurt even worse
than getting shot!
Aw!
Your Honor, permission
to hug the witness?
Granted.
Don't worry,
Mr. Griffin.
You're every bit
as sympathetic
as this chubby-cheeked
cocoa angel.
I haven't been listening.
What's goin' on?
I don't think it's
lost on any of us
that the laws are
written on white paper.
Yeah, white paper.
Check your jacket pocket.
"I don't think it's
lost on any of us
that the laws are
written on white paper."
Hey, look,
I'm just saying,
it's no surprise that
justice isn't colorblind.
Check your other
jacket pocket.
"Hey, look, I'm just saying
it's no surprise that
justice isn't colorblind."
Stewie, you're a jerk!
Check Chris' pocket.
What? There's nothing
in here, and...
Oh, God, the bottom of the
pocket's been cut out!
Thanks, Brian!
I was the mastermind
behind this whole thing!
Your witness.
All right, watch this.
This is where we take control
of the situation.
Mr. Brown, you testified
that you were listening to music
at the time of the shooting.
That's right.
And isn't Jay-Z music?
Yes.
And doesn't he have the lyrics,
"I put the gun to you.
"I'll kill ya, I'll chop ya up,
put ya inside the mattress
like drug money"?
I was listening
to Neil Sedaka's Hanukkah album.
And isn't true
that your last name
is the same
as Chris Brown's?
Yes, but I don't see what--
And what did Chris Brown
do to Rihanna?
He hit her, like,
a hundred times.
Your Honor, I'd like
to enter into evidence
this photo of a
badly beaten Rihanna
as well as this print ad
for the Entourage movie.
Why?!
I can't unsee this!
Who is this for?!
What's he doing?
He's making Cleveland Jr.
look like a thug.
I know.
That's the idea.
You don't want to go
back to jail, do you?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Mr. Brown, please
pick up this knife.
Aah!
He's got a knife!
This isn't fair!
They're making my son
look like a common hoodlum!
Joe, you're a cop!
Do something!
No, the soap
covers everything.
You might see, like, the
very top of the crack,
but that's-that's
not what it's about.
How do you sleep
at night?
Propped up on pillows,
on account of my fat throat.
If I lay flat on
my back, I die.
I need pillows
between my thighs myself.
And this friendship
is over!
Thanks for letting me
sit in the back.
I was flipping people
off the whole way.
Get out of here,
all of you!
My son didn't do
anything wrong!
Carter, I think this has
all kind of gone too far.
What do you think
you're doing?
I'm gonna make this right.
Everyone!
Listen, I have
something to say.
Cleveland Jr. doesn't
deserve any of this.
All those things you heard
about Cleveland Jr. were lies.
He didn't do anything to me.
He's a good kid,
from a good family.
I just got scared,
and I did something stupid.
I swear, it had nothing to do
with the color of his skin,
but... I did shoot him.
I deserve to be held
responsible for my actions.
Even if that means
going to jail.
You heard him,
other cops.
Let's take him in.
He doesn't know
our names, does he?
I don't think he does.
Wait a minute.
Peter didn't shoot my son.
I did.
Peter was just taking
the blame for me.
He's a good friend.
Eh, Mr. Brown,
what exactly are you saying?
I'm saying that I,
Cleveland Brown,
a black man,
shot Cleveland Brown, Jr.,
another black man.
Wait, wh-where
did everybody go?
You want to make
the media go away?
Just mention
black-on-black crime.
Boy, the world
we live in, huh?
Brian, reach into
Meg's pocket.
Go ahead, Brian.
I-I-I don't want to.
Cleveland,
why did you do that?
Peter, since this is about
racism, why don't we take
a slow, hands-clasped-behind-
the-back walk together?
Listen, I know you wouldn't
have shot Cleveland Jr.
on account of his race.
You shot him because
you're stupid.
That's all
I'm trying to say!
And I know you don't
have hate in your heart.
You were willing to go to jail
for shooting my son.
You took responsibility.
That's what's important.
So... you forgive me?
Of course I do.
Oh, thanks, Cleveland.
Hey, how you
feeling there, champ?
I'm good.
Getting better
every day.
Aw, I'm happy
to hear that.
Look, I-I hope
you know I'm sorry.
Hey, these things happen.
That's my boy.
Mr. Griffin?
Yeah?
Just so you know,
I'm gonna be coming
for your ass.
Wh-What's that now?
I'm saying it's on!
You ever feel the cool steel
of a switchblade
pressed against your temple?
He Mr. Griffin,
I'm just kidding.
Or am I?
You're gonna wonder about that,
you fat bitch.
See you later!
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru